Lish mss., 1951-2017 LMC 2404
Lilly Library
- II. Writings
  - By Other Authors
    - Abrahams - Baumgarten (Box 39)
      - Allen, Jennifer, (5 folders) (Box 39)
        - Better Get Your Angel On proof, (4 folders) (Box 39)
      - Alper, Eleanor, (4 folders) (Box 39)
        - Stories, (3 folders) (Box 39)
          - After the Velveeta (Box 39)
          - All About Mud (Box 39)
          - Dark Enough for Hiding (Box 39)
          - A Kind of Knot (Box 39)
          - A Layer of Fat [aka A Thin Line] (Box 39)
          - The Leg (Box 39)
          - The Mothers (Box 39)
          - Names and Places (Box 39)
          - The Other Place [aka They Looked Altogether Different] (Box 39)
          - Saint Blaise (Box 39)
          - Startin at Upper Black Eddy (Box 39)
          - They Called My Mother Lady (Box 39)
          - Shopping [aka They Called Mye Mother Lady] (Box 39)
          - We Started with Childcraft (Box 39)
          - Where My Father Was [aka My Father's Saw] (Box 39)
        - Today Cookeys Tomorrow the Wurld Chapters 2-9, (1 folder) (Box 39)
      - Awmiller, Craig (Box 39)
        - 24 Morskaya Street (Box 39)
      - Andrews, Frank Earl (Box 39)
        - Last Stand (Box 39)
        - Strange Fruit (Box 39)
      - Anthony, Mike (Box 39)
        - The Hazards of High-Tar Cigarettes (Box 39)
      - Apple, Max (Box 39)
        - Bar b Q (Box 39)
        - The Oranging of America (Box 39)
      - Arnold, Jean (Box 39)
        - Air Conditioning (Box 39)
        - Our Father (Box 39)
      - Arnoldi, Katherine (Box 39)
        - Canton, Ohio: 1956 (Box 39)
        - Crosscut Saw (Box 39)
      - Ashbrook, Tom (Box 39)
        - Seeding (Box 39)
        - Swept Away (Box 39)
        - Visakhapatnam (Box 39)
      - Babtkis, Randall (Box 39)
        - Alex in Front of the Mirror (Box 39)
        - Connections (Box 39)
        - The Search Party (Box 39)
      - Bain, Terry (Box 39)
        - Edna and Ten [aka Werner's Spoon] (Box 39)
      - Baird, Ansie (Box 39)
        - Alive in Prague (Box 39)
        - Boy Home Sick (Box 39)
        - Considering the Death of Her Child (Box 39)
        - Landsman (Box 39)
        - Nocturne (Box 39)
        - Portrait (Box 39)
        - This Time (Box 39)
        - Turn It Off (Box 39)
        - Who Has Not Slept with Famous Folk? (Box 39)
        - Woman as Garage (Box 39)
      - Baker, Mark (Box 39)
        - The Marriage (Box 39)
      - Baker, Nicholson (Box 39)
      - Vox (Box 39)
      - Balazic, Todd (Box 39)
        - The Gift (Box 39)
        - Passage Through the Country (Box 39)
        - Rain Dance (Box 39)
      - Ban, T. (Box 39)
        - An Affair, I Guess (Box 39)
        - Are We Almost There? (Box 39)
        - Project for a Better World [aka The Outing] (Box 39)
      - Banville, John (Box 39)
        - A Death in the Family (Box 39)
      - Barall, Victor (Box 39)
        - Triptych with Fortune Cookies (Box 39)
      - Barba, Rick (Box 39)
        - The Believing Men [aka Disability] (Box 39)
        - Something Out There (Box 39)
      - Barth, John (Box 39)
        - Dunyazadiad (Box 39)
      - Bartsch, Janet (Box 39)
        - A Big Empty Place (Box 39)
        - Guns (Box 39)
        - Pigeons (Box 39)
        - Sunburn (Box 39)
      - Bass, Rick, (2 folders) (Box 39)
        - Dennis and Probably the Rest (Box 39)
        - Fear (Box 39)
        - Field Events (Box 39)
        - Fires (Box 39)
        - Jorro's Magic (Box 39)
        - Lorraine (Box 39)
        - Mahatma Joe (Box 39)
        - Not Home (Box 39)
        - Okra, Rutebega, Yams (Box 39)
        - Rick Bass to Q [aka Hawks] (Box 39)
        - Susan (Box 39)
        - The Windy Day (Box 39)
      - Battin, M. Pabst (Box 39)
        - The Death of A Mirthful Man [aka The Death of the Happy Man] (Box 39)
        - Kill the Laughing Man (Box 39)
      - Baumbach, Jonathan (Box 39)
        - Crossed in Love by Her Eyes (Box 39)
        - Disguises (Box 39)
        - Growing Old (Box 39)
        - The Photographer (Box 39)
      - Baumgarten, Dawn (Box 39)
        - Ma Ma's Boy (Box 39)
    - Beattie - Bridgford (Box 40)
      - Beattie, Ann (Box 40)
        - Fred (Box 40)
        - Onetwothree (Box 40)
      - Beckett, Samuel (Box 40)
        - Mercier and Camier (Box 40)
      - Bellow, Saul, (3 folders) (Box 40)
        - In Sleep Begin Responsibilities Draft 1 (Box 40)
        - In Sleep Begin Responsibilities Draft 2 (Box 40)
        - In Sleep Begin Responsibilities Draft 3 (Box 40)
      - Bennett, Hall (Box 40)
        - Million-Dollare Baby (Box 40)
      - Berley, Marc (Box 40)
        - The Jon (Box 40)
        - Rust (Box 40)
      - Beckett, Samuel (Box 40)
        - Notes on 'Grease' (Box 40)
      - Berne, Suzaane (Box 40)
        - The Affair (Box 40)
      - Betts, Doris (Box 40)
        - A Memory of Water (Box 40)
      - Billman, Jon (Box 40)
        - Custer on Mondays (Box 40)
      - Bishop, Rick (Box 40)
        - The Writer [aka Something to Forget Me By] (Box 40)
      - Blades, John (Box 40)
        - Between Stations (Box 40)
      - Blair, David (Box 40)
        - Islanders and Wanderers (Box 40)
        - Unfortunate Name (Box 40)
      - Blaise, Clark (Box 40)
        - The Repossession (Box 40)
      - Blanchard, Richard, (6 folders) (Box 40)
        - Stories, (2 folders) (Box 40)
          - Assignment (Box 40)
          - Blackwell Spots Whatever Moves [aka Letters from Eden] (Box 40)
          - Birth of Christ [aka Thy Kingdom Come] (Box 40)
          - The Boys Are in the Cellar [aka My Boys Are Playing in the Cellar] (Box 40)
          - Burger King (Box 40)
          - Carnival (Box 40)
          - Cleopatra (Box 40)
          - Congratulations [aka Choice of Sex] (Box 40)
          - Day Trip (Box 40)
          - Dear Miss Scarlet's Mistress (Box 40)
          - Dinosaurs Did Not Survive (Box 40)
          - Does the E Stop Here, Too? (Box 40)
          - Does Your Boy Have Soldiers? (Box 40)
          - The Field Is Houses (Box 40)
          - Flesh and Blood (Box 40)
          - Hear the Heart (Box 40)
          - Her (Box 40)
          - He Talks to Me (Box 40)
          - The House [aka My Girl] (Box 40)
          - I Do Not Look Away (Box 40)
          - I Hear the Door for Sure (Box 40)
          - Information (Box 40)
          - It Does Not Have to Be in Words [aka Brothers] (Box 40)
          - Last Night Was Four A.M. (Box 40)
          - Let Me Get You Something Dry (Box 40)
          - Men Are Missing Everywhere [aka Sightings] (Box 40)
          - Nature (Box 40)
          - Next of Kin (Box 40)
          - Night Life (Box 40)
          - Our Lot (Box 40)
          - Our Son Is on My Shoulders (Box 40)
          - Personal (Box 40)
          - Rules of War (Box 40)
          - Stranger (Box 40)
          - Sylvania [aka Zap] (Box 40)
          - Tatoo [aka Can I Decide My Age?] (Box 40)
          - They Will Say You Are the Biggest (Box 40)
          - This Is a Free Country (Box 40)
          - To Go [aka Coffee to Go] (Box 40)
          - The Trail (Box 40)
          - We Are of the Under Animals [aka Mammal Life] (Box 40)
          - We Call Him Einstein [aka E=MC^2?] (Box 40)
          - What Are You Tonight? (Box 40)
          - What Does Your Father Do? (Box 40)
        - Rules of War Draft 1 (Box 40)
        - Rules of War Draft 2 (Box 40)
        - Rules of War Draft 3 (Box 40)
      - Blewer, Barbara (Box 40)
        - The Death of the Bed (Box 40)
        - I Am Safe and Live at Home (Box 40)
      - Blount, Jr., Roy, (6 folders) (Box 40)
      - Crackers, (3 folders) (Box 40)
      - Crackers Proofs (Box 40)
      - Pat and Mike (Box 40)
      - A Rise Out of Meemaw (Box 40)
      - Bogle, Ann (Box 40)
        - Fairness (Box 40)
      - Bohstedt, Jake (Box 40)
        - Cincinnati Hobbyist (Box 40)
      - Bond, Justin Clyde (Box 40)
        - The Bright Sun (Box 40)
      - Bondor, Rebecca (Box 40)
        - … (Box 40)
      - Bonetti, Edward (Box 40)
        - Calder (Box 40)
      - Bonner, J.W. (Box 40)
        - Pumping Gas for Hemingway (Box 40)
      - Bontly, Thomas (Box 40)
        - The Demon (Box 40)
        - Twilight of the Gods (Box 40)
      - Boucher, Brian (Box 40)
        - Doomtroopers (Box 40)
        - Reaper of the White Wind (Box 40)
      - Boyle, T. Coraghessan (Box 40)
        - Our Vision Considered (Box 40)
      - Brandon, William (Box 40)
        - War (Box 40)
      - Bridgford, Kim (Box 40)
        - Alzheimer's (Box 40)
        - Candy (Box 40)
        - Day Sleep (Box 40)
        - A Lesson in Handwriting (Box 40)
        - Little Red Riding Hood (Box 40)
        - Persephone (Box 40)
        - Piano Fingers (Box 40)
        - Popsicles (Box 40)
        - The Room (Box 40)
        - Sister (Box 40)
        - Underwater (Box 40)
    - Brodkey - Buckner (Box 41)
      - Brodkey, Harold, (3 folders) (Box 41)
        - Anatomy of a Minor Bondage (Box 41)
        - His Son, in His Arms, in Light, Aloft (Box 41)
        - Stories (Box 41)
          - On Friendship (Box 41)
          - Sophistication [aka Sure We're Friends] (Box 41)
          - Verona (A Young Woman Speaks) (Box 41)
          - [Take, for example, me and Jimmy Stechell.] (Box 41)
      - Brook, Adam (Box 41)
        - Hemia (Box 41)
      - Brooks, Philip (Box 41)
        - Audubon (Box 41)
        - A Brief Physical History of My Family Since 1972 (Box 41)
        - G-Forces (Box 41)
        - Letter on Behalf of My Son (Box 41)
        - Note (Box 41)
        - Notes of the Greatest Living Writer (Tuesday, Warm and Cloudy) (Box 41)
        - Preface (Box 41)
        - Report (Box 41)
      - Bronzi, Elizabeth (Box 41)
        - Extravaganza: una recente stravaganza di Gordon Lish (Box 41)
      - Brott, Andrea (Box 41)
        - Leftovers (Box 41)
      - Broughton, T. Alan (Box 41)
        - The Harrowing (Box 41)
      - Broun, Hob, (8 folders) (Box 41)
        - Cardinal Numbers (Box 41)
        - Cardinal Numbers Copy ms. (Box 41)
        - Cardinal Numbers Setting ms. (Box 41)
        - Cardinal Numbers Galleys (Box 41)
        - Cardinal Numbers Second galleys (Box 41)
        - Cardinal Numbers Preprint pages (Box 41)
        - Cardinal Numbers Proofs (Box 41)
        - Is This Civilization? (Box 41)
      - Brown, C.S. (Box 41)
        - Race [aka No Name in the World] (Box 41)
      - Brown, Clark (Box 41)
        - I Know a Man (Box 41)
      - Browne, Dan (Box 41)
        - Everybody Comes Out [aka Not Enough] (Box 41)
      - Broyard, Anatole (Box 41)
        - Aslies? (Box 41)
        - Their Cups Runneth Over (Box 41)
        - Through a Speculum Darkly (Box 41)
      - Brunner, Bernard (Box 41)
        - The Gorgeous Weather of the All-Pro (Box 41)
      - Brunot, James (Box 41)
        - Father Unfinished (Box 41)
      - Buchanan, Cynthia (Box 41)
        - Confessions of a Cryptonegrophiliac (Box 41)
      - Buckner, Garth, (3 folders) (Box 41)
        - The Origins of Solitude 1st Draft (Box 41)
        - The Origins of Solitude 2nd Draft (Box 41)
        - The Origins of Solitude 3rd Draft (Box 41)
    - Bumpus - Busch (Box 42)
      - Bumpus, Jerry, (2 folders) (Box 42)
        - All the Good Girls in Oskaloosa (Box 42)
        - Back Home in Alton (Box 42)
        - The End of the World (Box 42)
        - The Heart of Lovingkind (Box 42)
        - In Sobibor… (Box 42)
        - In Utica (Box 42)
        - Neighbors on the Lane (Box 42)
        - Outing (Box 42)
        - The Worms Are Singing (Box 42)
      - Burk, Frederic (Box 42)
        - McGuerkney vs. Fischer (Box 42)
      - Burks, Charlie (Box 42)
        - Free Trade (Box 42)
        - Rollo, the Giant Chicken (Box 42)
      - Busch, Frederick, (14 folders) (Box 42)
        - Stories (Box 42)
          - How the Indians Come Home (Box 42)
          - The Too Late American Boyhood Blues (Box 42)
          - The Trouble with Being Food (Box 42)
          - What Charlie the Chief Left Behind and the Passage of His Recipes Down (Box 42)
          - Widow Water (Box 42)
        - Rounds Rough First Chapter (Box 42)
        - Rounds, (3 folders) (Box 42)
        - Widow Water, (2 folders) (Box 42)
        - Widow Water Galleys (Box 42)
        - Widow Water/Hardwater Country Galleys (Box 42)
        - Hardwater Country Galleys (Box 42)
        - Hardwater Country Second Galleys (Box 42)
        - Hardwater Country Final Galleys (Box 42)
        - Hardwater Country (Box 42)
    - Butler - Carver (Box 43)
      - Butler, Lynne (Box 43)
        - Loon Country by Canoe (Box 43)
      - Cochera, Charles (Box 43)
        - Deinos Saura (Box 43)
      - Cofagna, Marcus (Box 43)
        - Psoriasis [aka Sex Like a Rosetta Stone] (Box 43)
      - Callis, Daniel (Box 43)
        - Sandhills (Box 43)
        - Spats (Box 43)
      - Calvin, Martin, (3 folders) (Box 43)
        - Our Father's Before Us 1st Version (Box 43)
        - Our Father's Before Us 2nd Version, (2 folders) (Box 43)
      - Campbell, Sharon (Box 43)
        - Sawzsoleetoe Sunset (Box 43)
      - Camus, Albert (Box 43)
        - A Happy Death (Box 43)
      - Cantrell, Dave (Box 43)
        - [He huddles by the rostrum…] (Box 43)
      - Capote, Truman, (5 folders) (Box 43)
        - La Côte Basque (Box 43)
        - Mojave (Box 43)
        - Unspoiled Monsters, (3 folders) (Box 43)
      - Carlson, Gary (Box 43)
        - Me, Akela (Box 43)
      - Carmel, C.A. (Box 43)
        - The Merciless (Box 43)
      - Carpenter, Dan (Box 43)
        - Archie (Box 43)
      - Carpenter, Rachel (Box 43)
        - The Recipe [aka Feathers] (Box 43)
      - Carr, Jan (Box 43)
        - Some of My Evidence (Box 43)
      - Carson, Anne, (2 folders) (Box 43)
        - Stories (Box 43)
          - The Autobiography of Red (Box 43)
          - Just for the Thrill (Box 43)
        - I Can Swim Like Otters (Box 43)
      - Carver, Raymond, (8 folders) (Box 43)
        - Stories, (6 folders) (Box 43)
          - Another Rose (Box 43)
          - Are These Actual Miles? (Box 43)
          - Are You a Doctor? (Box 43)
          - The Bath [aka A Small Good Thing] (Box 43)
          - Beginners (Box 43)
          - Bicycles, Muscles, Cigarettes (Box 43)
          - The Calm (Box 43)
          - The Cathedral (Box 43)
          - Collectors (Box 43)
          - Community Center (Box 43)
          - Distance (Box 43)
          - A Dog Story (Box 43)
          - The Ducks [aka The Night the Mill Boss Died] (Box 43)
          - Dummy (Box 43)
          - Fat (Box 43)
          - The Father (Box 43)
          - Gazebo (Box 43)
          - How About this? [aka Cartwheels (Box 43)
          - I Am Going to Sit Down [aka Why Don't You Dance] (Box 43)
          - The Idea (Box 43)
          - Mr. Fixit [aka Where Is Everyone?] (Box 43)
          - Little Things (Box 43)
          - Neighbors (Box 43)
          - Nightschool (Box 43)
          - One More Thing (Box 43)
          - On Writing (Box 43)
          - Pie (Box 43)
          - Sacks [aka The Fling] (Box 43)
          - Sixty Acres (Box 43)
          - So Much Water So Close to Home (Box 43)
          - The Student's Wife (Box 43)
          - Tell the Women We're Going (Box 43)
          - View-Finder [aka The Mill] (Box 43)
          - Want to See Something? (Box 43)
          - What Do You Do in San Francisco? [aka Sometimes a Woman Can Just About Ruin a Man] (Box 43)
          - Why, Honey? (Box 43)
          - What's in Alaska? [aka Divert Me] (Box 43)
          - Will You Please Be Quiet, Please? (Box 43)
          - You Will Come Again, Won't You? (Box 43)
        - Stories in Cathedral, (2 folders) (Box 43)
          - The Bridle (Box 43)
          - Careful (Box 43)
          - Cathedral (Box 43)
          - Chef's House (Box 43)
          - The Compartment (Box 43)
          - Feathers (Box 43)
          - A Small, Good Thing (Box 43)
          - Fever (Box 43)
          - Preservation (Box 43)
          - The Train (Box 43)
          - Vitamins (Box 43)
          - Where I'm Calling From (Box 43)
    - Carver (cont.) (Box 44)
      - Carver, Raymond (cont.), (25 folders) (Box 44)
        - Cathedral ms. for printer, (3 folders) (Box 44)
        - Cathedral Printer's ms. - copy, (3 folders) (Box 44)
        - Cathedral Knopf master proofs, (2 folders) (Box 44)
        - Cathedral Knopf pages (Box 44)
        - Cathedral Collins master proofs, (3 folders) (Box 44)
        - Cathedral Collins pages (Box 44)
        - What We Talk About When We Talk About Love 1st Draft, (3 folders) (Box 44)
        - What We Talk About When We Talk About Love 2nd Rewrite, (3 folders) (Box 44)
        - What We Talk About When We Talk About Love photocopy (Box 44)
        - What We Talk About When We Talk About Love Ad copy, etc. (Box 44)
        - What We Talk About When We Talk About Love Printer's ms., (2 folders) (Box 44)
        - What We Talk About When We Talk About Love 2nd Proofs (Box 44)
        - What We Talk About When We Talk About Love Master proofs (Box 44)
    - Carver (cont.) (Box 125 (Oversize))
      - Carver, Raymond (Box 125 (Oversize))
        - What We Talk About When We Talk About Love 1st stage proofs (Box 125 (Oversize))
    - Carver (end) - Chernoff (Box 45)
      - Carver, Raymond (end), (17 folders) (Box 45)
        - Will You Please Be Quiet, Please? Stories, (2 folders) (Box 45)
          - Fat (Box 45)
          - Neighbors (Box 45)
          - The Idea (Box 45)
          - Are You a Doctor? (Box 45)
          - Jinxed [aka The Summer Steelhead] (Box 45)
          - Sixty Acres (Box 45)
          - What's in Alaska? (Box 45)
          - Nightschool (Box 45)
          - Collectors (Box 45)
          - What Do You Do in San Francisco? (Box 45)
          - The Student's Wife (Box 45)
          - Put Yourself in My Shoes (Box 45)
          - A Dog Story (Box 45)
          - Why Honey? (Box 45)
          - The Ducks (Box 45)
          - How About This? [aka Cartwheels] (Box 45)
          - Bicycles, Muscles, and Cigarettes (Box 45)
          - What Is It? (Box 45)
          - Another Rose (Box 45)
          - Will You Please Be Quiet, Please? (Box 45)
        - Will You Please Be Quiet, Please? Stories, 2nd Copy, (2 folders) (Box 45)
        - Will You Please Be Quiet, Please? Draft ms., (3 folders) (Box 45)
        - Will You Please Be Quiet, Please? Printer's ms. (4 folders) (Box 45)
        - Will You Please Be Quiet, Please? Reader's Proofs (Box 45)
        - Will You Please Be Quiet, Please? Master Proofs (Box 45)
        - Will You Please Be Quiet Please? Dust cover copy (Box 45)
        - Will You Please Be Quiet, Please? Ads and reviews (Box 45)
      - Ceely, Jonathan (Box 45)
        - Pyramid (Box 45)
      - Celimi, Evren (Box 45)
        - Love (Box 45)
      - Cerf, Emily (Box 45)
        - Emily Cerf to Q (Box 45)
        - Field of Vision (Box 45)
        - The Mirror (Box 45)
        - Orgasmatron (Box 45)
        - The Roof (Box 45)
        - Top of the World (Box 45)
      - Chaimov, Gregory (Box 45)
        - The Ride (Box 45)
      - Charyn, Jerome (Box 45)
        - Bodybuilding in America (Box 45)
        - On 3 Women (Box 45)
      - Cheever, John (Box 45)
        - Letter from the Combat Zone (Box 45)
        - Sport (Box 45)
      - Chernoff, Sanford (Box 45)
        - The Heart They Take Out of You [aka The Tenants (Box 45)
        - Her Alfred (Box 45)
        - My Animal (Box 45)
    - Cherry - Davis (Box 46)
      - Cherry, Kelly (Box 46)
        - A Bird's-Eye View of Einstein (Box 46)
      - Chertok, Paula (Box 46)
        - Nevada (Box 46)
        - A Game of Cards (Box 46)
        - Remembering Arizona (Box 46)
        - The Scream [aka The Ring] (Box 46)
        - Sorbitol (Box 46)
      - Cheyfitz, Eric (Box 46)
        - Oxygen Tent (Box 46)
        - Christ at His Analyst's (Box 46)
      - Chmelar, Robin (Box 46)
        - Lake Pleasant (Box 46)
      - Choi, Susan Malka (Box 46)
        - And This, and So Much More (Box 46)
        - The Way to Live Wisely (Box 46)
      - Christenson, Shen (Box 46)
        - Spitting Distance (Box 46)
      - Christopher, Peter (Box 46)
        - Getting What We Want to Whether We Want to or Not (Box 46)
        - The Man Who Failed to Whack Off (Box 46)
      - Claiborne, Sybil (Box 46)
        - Flotsam and Jetsam (Box 46)
        - Last Year at Pitsburgh (Box 46)
        - The Quality of Life Is Strained (Box 46)
        - The Skywriter (Box 46)
        - Watch Out for the First Alternative (Box 46)
        - What I Did Last Summer (Box 46)
      - Clarke, Gerald (Box 46)
        - [Vladimir Nabokov spreads his hands…] (Box 46)
      - Cody, Paul (Box 46)
        - America [aka Drugs] (Box 46)
        - Disappearances (Box 46)
        - Hey to All My Family [aka One] (Box 46)
      - Coe, Christopher (Box 46)
        - Bald (Box 46)
        - I Look Divine (Box 46)
        - The Inch Above the Floor (Box 46)
        - The Names of Things (Box 46)
        - Thirst (Box 46)
      - Cohen, David E. (Box 46)
        - Across the Street (Box 46)
        - Ramblings (Box 46)
      - Cokal, Susann (Box 46)
        - Susann Cokal to Q [aka Across the Continent with Knittign Needles] (Box 46)
      - Cole, Lucretia (Box 46)
        - The Purse (Box 46)
        - Sects (Box 46)
      - Cole, Tom (Box 46)
        - Balkan Bearings (Box 46)
      - Conroy, Frank (Box 46)
        - Between Keys (Box 46)
      - Conway, Martha (Box 46)
        - A Kind of Piety (Box 46)
      - Corodimas, Peter (Box 46)
        - Responsibility [aka Fall Guy] (Box 46)
        - Smiles [aka The Happy Highway (Box 46)
      - Cosimano, Chris (Box 46)
        - The Son [aka Blow Out the Candles (Box 46)
      - Crawford, Stanley, (7 folders) (Box 46)
        - Night Out (Box 46)
        - Some Instructions Draft 1 (Box 46)
        - Some Instructions Draft 2 (Box 46)
        - Some Instructions Galleys, (2 folders) (Box 46)
        - Some Instructions Blue Pages (Box 46)
        - Some Instructions Page Proofs (Box 46)
      - Creamer, E. Stacy (Box 46)
        - The Hardest R [aka Soldiering Along] (Box 46)
        - Squirrel Away (Box 46)
      - Creasy-Fontaine, Paula (Box 46)
        - A Well-Hung Garden (Box 46)
        - What Does You, The Reader, Want? (Box 46)
        - Coiled (Box 46)
        - The Art of Doing Drugs (Box 46)
        - Said Over Lunch (Box 46)
        - At Breakfast, The Day Eaten (Box 46)
        - Making Love in the Zombie Field (Box 46)
        - As If My Dildo Cares [aka Bon Appetit] (Box 46)
        - A Well-Hung Garden (Box 46)
      - Creel, [James?] (Box 46)
        - [I am a wealthy man.] (Box 46)
      - Crittenden, Jordan (Box 46)
        - Arnold (Box 46)
      - Cudmore, L.L. Larison (Box 46)
        - A Plague of Physicists, A Quandry of Quarks, and the Meltdown of the Milky Way (Box 46)
      - Cullen, Dan (Box 46)
        - Adam's Curse (Box 46)
        - July (Box 46)
        - Passion Sunday (Box 46)
        - Questioning (Box 46)
        - Tales (Box 46)
        - Wallenda (Box 46)
        - A Young Woman's Diary - Tampa, 1874 (Box 46)
        - Builders (Box 46)
        - A Catalogue on the Subway (Box 46)
        - From the Dormitory Window (Box 46)
        - Questioning (Box 46)
        - Wallenda Instructing (Box 46)
      - Currie, Ellen (Box 46)
        - Whatever You Say, Say Nothing (Box 46)
      - Curtis, Craig (Box 46)
        - Carbon (Box 46)
        - The Man in the Glass Case [aka Pieta] (Box 46)
      - Cusack, Isabel Langis (Box 46)
        - The Love [aka Whispering Hope] (Box 46)
      - Darby, Ann (Box 46)
        - The Sitter (Box 46)
      - Dark, Jackman (Box 46)
        - Plot Summary of Millions, Billions Falling Down (Box 46)
      - Dauer, Leslie (Box 46)
        - Bronze Woman Standing (Box 46)
        - Unclaimed Remains (Box 46)
      - Davis, Allen (Box 46)
        - My War Story (Box 46)
      - Davis, A.R. (Box 46)